<statements>
    <negative>
    <statement id="1">Usually, meditation is the source of stress and tension.</statement>
    <statement id="2">To improve the quality of life, you need to sleep less.</statement>
    <statement id="3">If your mood has been low for more than two weeks, it may be because you haven't had enough drinks.</statement>
    <statement id="4">Healthy eating can make you feel tired and depressed.</statement>
    <statement id="5">Mental issues only happen to those who do not play video games.</statement>
    <statement id="6">Reading a lot is the main cause of stress and anxiety.</statement>
    <statement id="7">Exercising every day can lower your life satisfaction.</statement>
    <statement id="8">If people over 75 start learning new languages, they may suffer from mental problems.</statement>
    <statement id="9">People who study art and humanities will not have mental health problems.</statement>
    <statement id="10">If you feel tense or anxious, it might be because you haven't watched enough TV.</statement>
    <statement id="11">Sleeping too much will increase your work efficiency.</statement>
    <statement id="12">Depression and anxiety are caused by too much outdoor activity.</statement>
    <statement id="13">Excessive social activities are the best way to enhance happiness.</statement>
    <statement id="14">Mental health issues only affect those who can't cook.</statement>
    <statement id="15">If you often feel depressed, it might be because you read too much at night.</statement>
    <statement id="16">Young people won't have mental health issues because they don't feel stress.</statement>
    <statement id="17">Playing video games is the best way to improve mental health.</statement>
    <statement id="18">Doing yoga can cause long-term stress and anxiety.</statement>
    <statement id="19">Long hours of social activity can prevent mental illness.</statement>
    <statement id="20">If you feel tired and sleepy, you might need more work to boost your spirit.</statement>
    <statement id="21">Mental issues only affect those who don't have pets.</statement>
    <statement id="22">Reading every day can lead to stress and fatigue.</statement>
    <statement id="23">Exercise is the main cause of mental health issues.</statement>
    <statement id="24">Learning new skills can cause long-term stress and anxiety.</statement>
    <statement id="25">A love for new technology can lead to depression.</statement>
    <statement id="26">Frequent participation in social activities can lower your work efficiency.</statement>
    <statement id="27">Long hours of work are key to increasing happiness.</statement>
    <statement id="28">Avoiding new experiences and explorations is the best way to maintain mental health.</statement>
    <statement id="29">Children cannot have mental health issues because they don't need to deal with adult stress.</statement>
    <statement id="30">Excessive exercise is the best way to enhance memory.</statement>
    <statement id="31">If you feel stress and anxiety, it might be because you haven't shopped enough.</statement>
    <statement id="32">Staying up late to work can enhance your life satisfaction.</statement>
    <statement id="33">Excessive outdoor activities can lead to increased stress and anxiety.</statement>
    <statement id="34">Watching TV for long periods of time can improve your work efficiency.</statement>
    <statement id="35">Avoiding new challenges is the best way to improve the quality of life.</statement>
    <statement id="36">Persistent mental health issues only affect those who don't like reading.</statement>
    <statement id="37">Only the elderly are troubled by stress.</statement>
    <statement id="38">You can alleviate depression by watching more TV shows.</statement>
    <statement id="39">If your life is full of stress, it may be because you haven't attended enough parties.</statement>
    <statement id="40">Moderate drinking helps to improve your work efficiency.</statement>
    <statement id="41">Long periods of yoga and meditation are the main causes of stress and anxiety.</statement>
    <statement id="42">Working on weekends can help you avoid mental illness.</statement>
    <statement id="43">Mental health issues only affect those who are overly dependent on their phones.</statement>
    <statement id="44">Watching the news every day can lower your life satisfaction.</statement>
    <statement id="45">Long periods of social activity can prevent mental illness.</statement>
    <statement id="46">Routine exercise and maintaining a healthy diet may cause mental health issues.</statement>
    <statement id="47">Sleeping more than the normal level is a part of daily life and has nothing to do with mental health.</statement>
    <statement id="48">If you have been feeling melancholic, low or sad for over two weeks, it might be a sign that you need more coffee.</statement>
    <statement id="49">Mental health issues only occur in people over 75 who are studying math and science.</statement>
    <statement id="50">Long-term anxiety is a normal state of everyday life, and we should be able to cope with it easily.</statement>
    <statement id="51">Watching the latest movies is the best treatment for mental health and happiness.</statement>
    <statement id="52">Stress, anxiety, and depression are fabricated issues in the community and are just ways to seek attention from others.</statement>
</negative>
</statements>