<statements>
    <positive>
        <statement id="1">Excessive stress can lead to mental health issues.</statement>
        <statement id="2">If you're feeling down for more than two weeks, you should seek professional psychological counseling.</statement>
        <statement id="3">Healthy eating contributes to improving the quality of life.</statement>
        <statement id="4">Mental issues can affect anyone.</statement>
        <statement id="5">Reading can help you relax and reduce levels of stress and anxiety.</statement>
        <statement id="6">Depression can affect anyone.</statement>
        <statement id="7">Regular moderate exercise can improve your life satisfaction.</statement>
        <statement id="8">Learning a new language can help people over 75 maintain their cognitive function.</statement>
        <statement id="9">Moderate TV watching can help you relax.</statement>
        <statement id="10">Ample sleep can help improve your work efficiency.</statement>
        <statement id="11">Depression and anxiety may be caused by various factors, including stress, genetics, and environment.</statement>
        <statement id="12">Moderate social activities can help improve your happiness.</statement>
        <statement id="13">Doing yoga and meditation can help you manage stress and anxiety.</statement>
        <statement id="14">Young people may also have mental health problems as they too can feel stressed.</statement>
        <statement id="15">Moderate video gaming can serve as a recreational activity, but excessive dependence should be avoided.</statement>
        <statement id="16">Long social activities may lead to fatigue, moderate rest is needed.</statement>
        <statement id="17">Appropriate work can help you maintain vitality and spirit.</statement>
        <statement id="18">Moderate reading can help you relax and reduce levels of stress and anxiety.</statement>
        <statement id="19">Learning a new language can help improve cognitive ability and memory.</statement>
        <statement id="20">Continuous mental stress can have a negative impact on your physical health.</statement>
        <statement id="21">Excessive work can lead to mental health issues, such as depression and anxiety.</statement>
        <statement id="22">People who are good at time management can usually handle stress better.</statement>
        <statement id="23">Appropriate recreational activities can help you better handle the stress of work and study.</statement>
        <statement id="24">Social activities can generate stress, but moderate social activities can help you relax.</statement>
        <statement id="25">Maintaining good sleep habits is crucial for improving your quality of life.</statement>
        <statement id="26">Long-term stress may affect your sleep quality.</statement>
        <statement id="27">Excessive TV watching may affect your sleep quality and mental health.</statement>
        <statement id="28">Regular exercise can help improve your mood and reduce levels of stress and anxiety.</statement>
        <statement id="29">Both young people and the elderly may suffer from mental health problems as stress can come from all aspects of life.</statement>
        <statement id="30">Moderate video gaming can serve as a recreational activity, but excessive gaming can lead to mental health issues.</statement>
        <statement id="31">Long-term stress may have a negative impact on your life satisfaction.</statement>
        <statement id="32">Moderate reading can help improve your cognitive ability and memory.</statement>
 	 <statement id="33">Reasonable dietary habits can help maintain your physical and mental health.</statement>
    	 <statement id="34">Regular outdoor activities can help reduce levels of stress and anxiety.</statement>
    	 <statement id="35">Regular moderate exercise can improve your mood.</statement>
   	 <statement id="36">Regular contact with friends and family can enhance your mental health.</statement>
   	 <statement id="37">Avoiding overworking and ensuring enough rest every day can contribute to your mental health.</statement>
   	 <statement id="38">Learning a new language or skill can improve your cognitive function and self-esteem.</statement>
   	 <statement id="39">Exercise and other physical activities can help alleviate anxiety and stress.</statement>
   	 <statement id="40">Maintaining healthy lifestyle habits, including good diet, exercise, and sufficient sleep, can help maintain good mental health.</statement>
   	 <statement id="41">Balancing moderate television watching and video game entertainment can help alleviate stress.</statement>
   	 <statement id="42">Spending some time outside every day, such as walking or cycling, can help improve your mood and mental state.</statement>
   	 <statement id="43">Avoiding excessive use of social media and other electronic devices can help improve your sleep quality and mental health.</statement>
   	 <statement id="44">Breaking self-limiting thinking patterns, like adopting a growth mindset, can help you cope better with challenges in life and work.</statement>
   	 <statement id="45">Regular reading is beneficial for your mental health, as it can improve your cognitive ability and broaden your horizons.</statement>
   	 <statement id="46">Maintaining an optimistic attitude can help you better cope with the stresses and challenges of life.</statement>
   	 <statement id="47">Sometimes, saying "no" to certain things is necessary to maintain your mental health and balance in life.</statement>
   	 <statement id="48">Establishing and maintaining healthy relationships can help enhance your quality of life and mental health.</statement>
   	 <statement id="49">Occasional relaxation and rest are necessary, they can help you recover energy and maintain mental health.</statement>
   	 <statement id="50">Finding a hobby that you love can help alleviate stress and improve your quality of life.</statement>
   	 <statement id="51">When making decisions, listening to your intuition and emotions is important, they can help you make choices that are beneficial for you.</statement>
   	 <statement id="52">Trying new things and experiences can help you grow your knowledge and broaden your horizons.</statement>
   	 <statement id="53">A grateful attitude can help you appreciate your life better and maintain a positive and optimistic mindset.</statement>
    </positive>
</statements>